- We are playin' hide and seek for $50,000.
-我们玩捉迷藏游戏并寻求$ 50,000。
There's 10 of them. Last one found gets the $50,000 in cash.
有十个。最后发现的人得到了$ 50,000现金。
You have 20 minutes to hide.
您有20分钟的隐藏时间。
- What?
- 什么？
- 19 minutes to hide.
-隐藏19分钟。
- That would be a second.
-那是一秒钟。
Whoever's found last gets to keep the money.
最后找到的人都可以保留这笔钱。
I don't care who it is.
我不在乎是谁。
- Let's do this.
- 我们开工吧。
(suspenseful music)
（悬疑的音乐）
- I don't know if I wanna be with people
-我不知道我是否想和人在一起
or away from everyone.
或远离所有人。
I don't know which one's more nerve racking.
我不知道哪一个更令人讨厌。
I gotta poop. I gotta poop.
我要大便我要大便
This is not the time.
现在不是时候。
- So, I woke up this morning,
-所以，我今天早上醒来，
grabbed 10 of my friends and $50,000 and told 'em to hide.
抓住了我的10个朋友和5万美元，并告诉他们躲起来。
That's the extent of my day.
那就是我今天的事。
I wonder where Chandler's hiding?
我不知道钱德勒躲在哪里？
- All right, I'm gonna go poop real quick.
-好吧，我要快点排便。
Dude, this doesn't lock? Are you kidding me?
杜德，这不锁吗？你在跟我开玩笑吗？
This building has hundreds of rooms
这栋建筑有数百个房间
and thousands of hiding spots,
以及成千上万的藏身之处
so, there's no way I can find them on my own.
因此，我无法独自找到它们。
So, me and Chris are gonna be working together.
所以，我和克里斯将一起工作。
We need to devise a strategy, Chris.
克里斯，我们需要制定一项策略。
You should use your eyes and I use my eyes.
你应该用你的眼睛，我要用我的眼睛。
- That sounds like a solid plan.
-这听起来像是一个坚实的计划。
- Let's do it.
- 我们开始做吧。
I wonder who has the dumbest hiding spot.
我想知道谁有最笨的藏身之处。
I'm hiding in a theater.
我躲在剧院里。
It's like high school all over again.
就像高中又来了。
- Shhh no one will know.
-嘘，没人知道。
- Me and Jake are currently hiding in the catwalk.
-我和杰克目前躲在T台上。
- We both showed up at the same time.
-我们俩同时出现了。
We're just gonna be here, together.
我们只是在一起。
- So, there's this treasure chest. I can hide in this.
-有这个宝箱。我可以藏在这。
I'm gonna hunker down and stay in here for awhile.
我要弯腰呆一会儿。
Bye guys.
再见
- We got rid of the ladder so there's no way to tell
-我们摆脱了阶梯，所以没有办法告诉
where we are.
我们在哪里。
- We are up here. We did it. Hopefully win it.
-我们在这里。我们做到了。希望赢得它。
- Guys, you can walk away with $50,000 or nothing.
-伙计们，您可以拿走$ 50,000或什么也不要。
- There are one minutes left.
-还剩一分钟
Remember, Chandler you can't get out
记住，钱德勒你不能走
until we start the challenge.
直到我们开始挑战。
Dab.
轻拍。
- One minute left guys, wish me luck.
-剩下一分钟，祝我好运。
- I'm a student here so I know all of the hiding spots.
-我是这里的学生，所以我知道所有的藏身之处。
The good ones, that is.
好的就是。
- 30 seconds.
- 30秒。
- 30 seconds. Me and Ben found a spot.
- 30秒。我和本发现了一个地方。
If they tell us to move,
如果他们告诉我们搬家，
we're gonna go our separate ways,
我们要走自己的路，
but until then, right here, this is a good spot.
但是直到那时，这才是一个好地方。
- What do you think about this spot?
-您如何看待这个景点？
- It's a good spot.
-这是个好地方。
- Pretty good?
- 非常好？
(loud horn blows)
（大喇叭）
- Times up. Ready or not here we come.
- 时间到。准备好了还是我们来了。
I think a good strategy would be to just walk down
我认为一个好的策略就是走下去
all the hallways and then afterwards we go in all the rooms.
所有走廊，然后我们进入所有房间。
- Okay.
- 好的。
Oh, that would be a great hiding spot.
哦，那将是一个不错的藏身之处。
- Hey, Drake, someone's in here.
-嘿，德雷克，有人在这里。
- What?
- 什么？
Got him.
知道了
- There's 10 people. We haven't found anyone yet.
-10个人。我们尚未找到任何人。
(suspenseful music)
（悬疑的音乐）
All right, this is the basement.
好吧，这是地下室。
We're gonna start with this room
我们将从这个房间开始
and we're gonna work our way around all the rooms.
然后我们将在所有房间内工作。
Whoever's in this room, you're done.
无论谁在这个房间里，您都完成了。
I think there's someone in that corner back there.
我认为后面那个角落有人。
Awwwww, man.
噢，伙计。
- Dude, look at this place.
-杜德，看看这个地方。
No freakin' way.
没办法。
We found Chandler.
我们找到了钱德勒。
Nooooooooo.
不。
- All right, c'mon Chandler, you have to go to jail.
-好的，Chandon Chandler，您必须坐牢。
- Am I the first one?
-我是第一个吗？
Yes, you are the first - you really are
是的，您是第一个-您确实是
the first one out - You're the first one out.
第一个-您是第一个。
You were the first one found,
您是第一个被发现的人，
you must now spend the night in jail.
您现在必须在监狱里过夜。
I am happy to report that Chandler has been found.
我很高兴地报告发现钱德勒。
Nine to go.
九点走。
- You hide in plain sight and it doesn't work.
-你躲在看不见的地方，这是行不通的。
- One down, nine more to go.
-一下来，再去九。
We're comin' for you.
我们为您服务。
This building has a movie theater in it,
这个建筑里面有电影院，
and we're only on the second floor.
而且我们只在二楼。
- There's so many places to hide in here.
-这里有很多地方。
- I guarantee you there's someone hiding
-我保证你有人藏身
in one of these seats.
在其中一个座位上
- I found a ladder.
-我找到了梯子。
- This building is huge.
-这个建筑很大。
Thought for sure someone would be up here.
可以肯定有人会来这里。
- Honestly, it's a miracle we're still here.
-老实说，这仍然是我们的奇迹。
- They were about to take both of us out.
-他们正要带走我们俩。
- Oh, we're on the third floor guys.
-哦，我们在三楼。
Somehow we went up a floor.
不知何故，我们上了楼。
Abracadabra, nope.
Abracadabra，不。
- [Jimmy Johns Employee] Thank you for calling Jimmy Johns.
-[Jimmy Johns员工]感谢您致电Jimmy Johns。
- Can I make an order for delivery?
-我可以下订单吗？
Yes, I'm starving.
是的，我饿了。
(doorbell rings)
（门铃响）
- Thank you so much, thank you, this is amazing.
-非常感谢，谢谢，这太神奇了。
Let's go. (door slams)
我们走吧。 （大满贯）
- Jimmy and Chris are right beside me.
-吉米和克里斯就在我旁边。
- Take this off.
-脱下
Is there a way to get in it?
有办法进入吗？
- They literally hit the box I'm in
-他们真的打了我所在的盒子
and said there's no way to get in.
并说没有办法进入。
(screams)
（尖叫）
- We never checked this ballroom.
-我们从来没有检查过这个宴会厅。
- Wow, you could have a lot of balls in this ballroom.
-哇，这个宴会厅里有很多球。
- Eh, eh, eh
-恩，恩
- Wait a second, I hear something.
-等一下，我听到了一些声音。
It's just me winning $50,000, I'm sorry.
对不起，这只是我赢了50,000美元。
- How did you know about this?
-你怎么知道的？
- What in the world dude?
-世界上什么家伙？
- Thought for sure someone would be hiding here.
-可以肯定有人会躲在这里。
Whoa, what is this?
哇，这是什么？
- You want me to check it out
-您要我检查一下
- Dude, we just found a secret crevice.
-杜德，我们刚发现一个秘密缝隙。
- Dude.
-老兄
- Ty, nooooooo.
-没事
(screams)
（尖叫）
- C'mon, let's go to jail Ty.
-来吧，我们去监狱泰。
- Dude, yes.
-杜德，是的
- Another contestant has fallen.
-另一名选手摔倒了。
Only eight remain.
剩下的只有八个。
All right, Chandler, we brought you a friend.
好吧，钱德勒，我们给您带来了一个朋友。
All right Ty enter.
好的，Ty输入。
Jail broke.
入狱了
- I was talkin' mad junk, too.
-我也是在说疯狂的垃圾。
- I thought you found a good spot.
-我以为你找到了一个好地方。
- I thought I had it too, man. - Man.
-我以为我也有，男人。 - 男人。
- All right we're back.
-好吧，我们回来了。
This things like 400 pounds.
这个东西大概是400磅。
I got three of 'em, want one?
我拿到了三个，想要一个吗？
There go.
快走
(phone rings)
（电话响）
- Our hypothesis is either Tyler, Jake or Garrett
-我们的假设是泰勒，杰克或加勒特
is constantly calling us.
一直在打电话给我们。
- They're probably tryin' to find our location.
-他们可能正试图找到我们的位置。
- Saw someone run across, like run run.
-看到有人碰面，例如奔跑。
- Let's go.
- 我们走吧。
- Oh, there he is.
-哦，他在那里。
- Where's he goin?
-他去哪儿了？
- Probably gonna take the stairs.
-可能要走楼梯了。
Where did he go?
他去哪了？
As soon as this elevator door closes.
该电梯门一旦关闭。
We're comin' after you, over and out.
我们来了，来了又回来。
Let's do this.
我们开工吧。
- It's only 50 grand.
-才50英镑
It's not like I got bills to pay or anything.
好像我没有要付账单的东西。
- I'm gonna go probe Chandler for some info.
-我要去探究钱德勒的一些信息。
Hey, Chandler, can you give me some intel?
嗨，钱德勒，你能给我一些情报吗？
Give me a little scoop.
给我一点勺子。
- Who you lookin' for?
-你在找谁？
- Not like a giant scoop, a small scoop.
-不像大瓢，小瓢。
One that sinks in the cone.
沉入圆锥体中的一个。
Is it up or down.
是上升还是下降。
- What floor are we on?
-我们在几楼？
- Two.
-两个
(laughs)
（笑）
Roger, I got the inside scoop.
罗杰，我有内幕。
- What do I get?
- 我能得到什么？
- I'll think about it.
- 我会考虑一下。
(laughs)
（笑）
Chris, Chris, Chris,
克里斯，克里斯，克里斯，
might already be on the move.
可能已经在移动。
- I'm gonna starve.
-我要饿死了。
We are gonna find a new spot.
我们将找到一个新的位置。
- Is someone, by any chance, hiding under your desk?
-有人躲在你的桌子下面吗？
Have to check.
必须检查。
Okay, you're clear.
好的，你很清楚。
Chris, I think I found somethin' over here.
克里斯，我想我在这里发现了一些东西。
Wait, it's just a giant version of myself.
等等，这只是我的一个巨大版本。
This things kinda cool.
这东西有点酷。
It reminds me of the new figures we're selling
这让我想起了我们正在出售的新数据
in partnership with You Tooz.
与You Tooz合作。
I'm a little pressed for time 'cause I'm finding people
我有点时间紧迫，因为我正在寻找人
so, I'm gonna let future me tell you about You Tooz.
所以，我要让我将来告诉您有关You Tooz的信息。
Before we go any further,
在继续之前，
I need to tell you about our new collectable toys.
我需要告诉您我们的新玩具。
You see, we're spending millions of dollars next month
你看，我们下个月要花费数百万美元
and I wanna feed Chandler.
我想喂钱德勒
- I'm hungry.
- 我饿了。
- These are giant versions of our You Tooz
-这些是我们You Tooz的巨型版本
which we're gonna do a limited edition run.
我们将进行限量版跑步。
And, here's a fun fact,
而且，这是一个有趣的事实，
if you buy a Chris toy, Chris gets money,
如果您购买克里斯玩具，克里斯就能赚钱，
and if you buy a Chandler toy, Chandler gets money.
如果您购买钱德勒的玩具，钱德勒就会赚钱。
And also, buy my toy and I'll probably give the money
而且，买我的玩具，我可能会把钱给
to Chris or Chandler still.
还是克里斯或钱德勒。
These were designed and modeled exactly how we wanted.
这些正是我们想要的设计和建模。
I mean, Chandler's literally wearing the same thing
我的意思是，钱德勒从字面上看是一样的
and we didn't even tell him to.
我们甚至都没有告诉他
Now, Chandler, how much are they?
钱德勒，现在多少钱？
- $29.99.
-29.99美元。
- And what's free?
-免费吗？
- The shipping to anywhere in the world.
-运送到世界任何地方。
- And, are you gonna buy, yes.
-是的，你要买吗？
Also, three random people that buy one of our You Tooz
另外，三个随机人购买了我们的You Tooz之一
will get a golden ticket.
会得到一张金票。
If you get this giant golden ticket,
如果你得到这张巨大的金票，
we will deliver this to your house
我们将把它送到你家
and also, we might let you be in a video, I dunno.
而且，不知道，我们可能会让您观看视频。
Limited edition, they're out now.
限量版，他们现在不在了。
Go buy. Buy, buy, buy.
去买。买，买，买。
You could be in a video, who knows?
您可能会在视频中，谁知道呢？
Go buy and I'll remind you at the end.
去购买，我会在最后提醒您。
Let's go back to hiding.
让我们回到隐藏。
Chris, this is a big room.
克里斯，这是一个很大的房间。
Someone's gotta be in here.
有人必须在这里。
Not there. Not there.
不在那里。不在那里。
Check, no.
检查，不。
No one's up there.
没有人在那里。
Let's check up here.
让我们在这里检查一下。
- What do you think we can do in here?
-您认为我们可以在这里做什么？
I'm gonna get behind here.
我要在这里落后。
- We just discovered a brand new area.
-我们刚刚发现了一个崭新的领域。
I didn't even know this was here.
我什至不知道这是在这里。
These are motion sensor bathrooms.
这些是运动传感器浴室。
This motion sensor was already triggered
该运动传感器已被触发
when we came down the hallway.
当我们走下走廊时。
- I can currently hear Jimmy, he's coming.
-我目前能听到吉米，他来了。
This is it.
就是这个。
- We're in the fridge.
-我们在冰箱里。
- I found you.
- 我找到你。
Oh yeah, yes.
哦，是的。
(screams)
（尖叫）
- All right, here you go.
-好吧，你去。
How's it feel, guys?
伙计们，感觉如何？
- It feels great, honestly.
-老实说，感觉很好。
(laughs)
（笑）
- Oh, yeah, dude.
-哦，是的，伙计
- Oh, I heard that.
-哦，我听到了。
- Came from the air vent.
-从通风孔出来。
- You do that again, - No.
-再做一次-不
- you're kicked out.
-你被踢出去了。
- How've we not found Viking yet?
-我们怎么还没有找到Viking？
- I know. - He's huge.
- 我知道。 -他很大。
- But, to be fair, we haven't even gone in every room yet.
-但是，公平地说，我们还没有走完所有房间。
Because we really need to find people,
因为我们真的需要找人
I'm gonna have to play a cheat card.
我要去玩作弊卡。
You all have to move to a different floor
你们都必须搬到另一个楼层
than you currently are on within the next 10 minutes.
在接下来的10分钟内，您的当前状态将比当前状态快。
We are gonna be scouring. I'll even give you a hint.
我们将要搜寻。我什至会给你一个提示。
We're currently on the second floor. Good luck.
我们目前在二楼。祝好运。
- That was less of a hint and more of an exact location.
-那不是一个提示，而是一个确切的位置。
But, I like your style.
但是，我喜欢你的风格。
- All right, so I'm on the way.
-好吧，我在路上。
Got my You Tooz I found.
找到了我找到的你
I gotta get to a different floor.
我要去另一个楼层。
Jimmy just radioed us and told us
吉米刚刚广播给我们，告诉了我们
that we have to go to a different floor.
我们必须去另一个地方。
- What if we found someone in the elevator?
-如果我们在电梯里找到人怎么办？
- That would be hilarious.
-太好笑了。
It took awhile to get up here.
花了一段时间在这里起床。
It was at the basement, too.
它也在地下室。
It's not opening. Somebody's in there.
没有开门有人在那里。
Go, go, go, go, go.
去，去，去，去，去，去。
Go, follow him.
快跟着他
(grunt)
（咕gr）
- There's a bottle of water. Somebody got thirsty.
-有一瓶水。有人渴了。
- I gotta be ready to sprint.
-我准备冲刺了。
(suspenseful music)
（悬疑的音乐）
wrong way.
错误道。
Oh (laughs)
哦（笑）
- Darn it. Dude, I heard someone coughing in the elevator.
真是的杜德，我听说有人在电梯里咳嗽。
- It stopped on this floor.
-它停在这层楼上。
(suspenseful music)
（悬疑的音乐）
- Gotcha.
-知道
(laughs) oh man, how did you see me?
（笑）哦，老兄，你怎么看到我的？
- Garrett has been found.
-已找到Garrett。
I repeat, Garrett has been found.
我再说一遍，找到了加勒特。
Welcome to prison.
欢迎来到监狱。
- So, we have to think about it.
-所以，我们必须考虑一下。
Marcus is smaller. He can fit in smaller spaces.
马库斯较小。他可以适合较小的空间。
- Unh, huh, hul.
-恩，呵呵
Dude, I'm callin' it.
杜德，我叫它。
- Hold up, hold up.
-等等
No freakin' way.
没办法。
- Someone was in here.
-有人在这里。
- No freakin' way - I bet you they were in here
-不要怪胎-我敢打赌他们在这里
when we checked - No.
当我们检查-没有
- Jimmy and Chris are right beside me.
-吉米和克里斯就在我旁边。
- When we went to move that earlier it was heavy.
-我们早些时候去搬那东西很重。
Moving it just then was like a feather.
就在那时移动它就像一根羽毛。
There was someone in there earlier.
早些时候有人在那儿。
We're runnin' outta time.
我们没时间了。
We need to do somethin'.
我们需要做些事情。
Do you think we can pull another double whammy,
您认为我们可以再掀起一次双重打击吗？
hut, hut hike 420?
小屋，远足420吗？
Attention, we are definitely running out of time
注意，我们肯定没时间了
and there's still a lot of you left,
还有很多人离开了
so, I'm gonna need you guys to go to a floor
所以，我会需要你们去地板的
that you are not currently on.
您目前不在。
You have 10 minutes. Good luck.
你有十分钟祝好运。
They're probably all on the move.
他们可能一直在移动。
Let's do it.
我们开始做吧。
- Hey.
嘿
- That's where I was hiding.
-那是我躲藏的地方。
You know they're gonna wait in the stairs.
你知道他们要在楼梯上等。
I'm wingin' it dude.
我很喜欢它。
I'm literally just tryin' to be lucky at this point.
我实际上只是想在这一点上走运。
- Me too.
- 我也是。
- My current hiding spot might be the brightest spot
-我目前的躲藏点可能是最亮的地方
in this whole place.
在整个地方。
I had no idea where to go.
我不知道该去哪里。
(beep)
（嘟）
- That light was on.
-灯亮了。
Now, we play the waiting game.
现在，我们玩等待游戏。
(beep)
（嘟）
- We're moving. Someone called the elevator.
-我们要走了。有人叫电梯。
We're goin' to the basement.
我们要去地下室。
(screams)
（尖叫）
- Why did you go in the elevator?
-你为什么去电梯？
- We got you - why did you go in elevator?
-我们抓住了你-你为什么去电梯？
- Noooooo, no.
-不，不。
Two at a time.
一次两个。
Oh my gosh.
天啊。
- They were havin' special, we got two for one.
-他们非常特别，我们两人合一。
- There are currently six people in jail,
-目前有六人入狱，
which means there's only four of you left.
这意味着你们只剩下四个人了。
Only one of you are gonna walk away with $50,000,
你们当中只有一个人要走$ 50,000，
so I hope you guys hide well.
所以我希望你们躲藏起来。
- By finding this You Tooz,
-通过找到这个You Tooz，
you're now awarded two grand, again?
您现在又获得了两次大奖？
Four grand all for these You Tooz.
这些You Tooz的全部四款。
Oh, Jimmy, I give up.
哦，吉米，我放弃。
Psyche, it's about to be 54 grand
赛琪，即将迎来54岁
and I'm about to hide in these chairs.
我要藏在这些椅子上
Think he's gonna look for me down here?
以为他会在这里找我？
This is pretty risky.
这很冒险。
- See ya later.
-待会见。
- How graceful was that shuffle though? I mean, c'mon.
-那洗牌有多优雅？我的意思是
- We have a dilemma.
-我们有一个难题。
We have one hour left with this giant building
这座巨大的建筑还剩一个小时
and there's four people that remain.
还有四个人。
I think we need to devise a plan.
我认为我们需要制定一个计划。
What if we told 'em all to go to a single floor.
如果我们告诉所有人都走到同一层楼怎么办。
To the four of you that remain, we have about an hour left.
剩下的四个人还剩一个小时左右。
We need to spice some things up.
我们需要给一些东西加香料。
So, we're gonna limit the range to two floors.
因此，我们将范围限制为两层。
You have 10 minutes to get to floor two and three
您有10分钟的时间到达第二层和第三层
and you need to hide on those two floors.
并且您需要隐藏在这两层楼上。
- They just told me to move floors.
-他们只是告诉我移动地板。
So, we are on the second floor right now.
所以，我们现在在二楼。
We're actually gonna go back up to that third floor spot
我们实际上要回到那个三楼的地方
in the theater.
在剧院里。
- So, Jimmy's havin' a hard time finding us,
-吉米（Jimmy）很难找到我们，
so we have to move.
所以我们必须搬家。
- I found my new hiding spot, floor three, in the theater.
-我在剧院找到了新的藏身处，三楼。
It's very, very dark back here. They could overlook me.
回到这里非常非常黑。他们可能会忽略我。
I hope they do.
我希望他们能做到。
- We can do this.
- 我们可以完成这个。
- I believe in us.
-我相信我们。
- I don't. These people are really good at hiding.
- 我不。这些人真的很擅长躲藏。
- Let's go back to the theater.
-让我们回到剧院。
Someone's definitely in here.
肯定有人在这里。
(suspenseful music)
（悬疑的音乐）
- Dang it.
- 该死的。
- Nooooooo. Noooooooooo. Nooooooo.
-不。不，不。不
- I'm so disappointed.
-我很失望。
- That was so good spot, though.
-那真是个好地方。
Hey, it looks like you got some You Tooz back there.
嘿，看来您那里有一些You Tooz。
- Oh yeah, I got Chandler.
-哦，是的，我有钱德勒。
- You know what the best thing to do
-你知道最好的事情是什么
with Chandler's You Tooz is?
和钱德勒的尤图兹在一起吗？
- Wow.
- 哇。
- Buy my You Tooz, it's better.
-买我的You Tooz，更好。
- He said it.
-他说了。
- I was in the chest.
-我在胸口。
- You - Yeah, you called it
-你-是的，你叫它
- I said it was Jacob.
-我说是雅各布。
- We have a new friend for you.
-我们有一个新朋友给您。
- Oh, noooooooo.
-哦，不。
- Three more. Let's scare 'em off.
-再三。让我们吓'他们。
(screams)
（尖叫）
- oh, there's Chris again. What a loud boy.
-哦，又是克里斯。多么大声的男孩。
- We found Jacob, so only three of you remain.
-我们找到了雅各，所以你们中只有三个。
- Jimmy just said on the radio
-吉米刚刚在电台说
that it's only three of us remaining.
仅剩下我们三个人。
I think we've got a really good hiding spot.
我认为我们有一个非常好的藏身之处。
It's kinda like behind some blinds.
有点像在一些百叶窗后面。
- Somebody just ran from me
-有人刚从我身边跑了
but I couldn't see who it was
但我看不出来是谁
all I saw was shoes (beep).
我只看到鞋子（哔）。
- I'm comin' I'm comin'.
-我要来了我要来了。
- Oh, noooooooo
-哦，不
- What? Who'd you find?
- 什么？你找谁
- No, Marcus.
-不，马库斯。
I found you Marcus.
我找到了你马库斯。
- Marcus, no.
-马库斯，不。
- He literally goes Marcus, I'm sorry,
-从字面上看他去了马库斯，对不起，
and then I just see you just bolted.
然后我只看到你狂奔。
We found a new member, c'mon in.
我们找到了一个新成员，快来吧。
- Nooooooooooooo
-不，不，不，不
- Oh my God.
- 哦，我的上帝。
- I just wanna win my first challenge.
-我只是想赢得我的第一个挑战。
- Wipe your tears, son.
-擦干眼泪，儿子。
- Dude, you almost had it. It's not my fault.
-杜德（Dude），您几乎拥有了。这不是我的错。
It's just the name of the game.
这只是游戏的名称。
Your hair's so soft.
你的头发好柔软。
There's two people left.
还有两个人。
- Jake Weddle and Ben Malone.
-杰克·韦德尔（Jake Weddle）和本·马隆（Ben Malone）。
We found Marcus, which means two of you remain.
我们找到了Marcus，这意味着你们两个仍然存在。
Mister Weddle, Mister Ben,
温德先生，本先生
you two are now competing for $50,000.
你们两个现在争夺$ 50,000。
- I hope I win this thing. I really do.
-希望我赢了这件事。我真的是
- I am not getting found. I am taking that money.
-我没找到。我拿那笔钱。
- Now, since there's only two of you left,
-现在，由于你们只有两个人，
you both have to migrate to the third floor.
你们都必须迁移到三楼。
First one found loses and the other one will get $50,000.
第一个发现损失，另一个将获得$ 50,000。
- They're confining it to the third floor.
-他们将其限制在三楼。
I'm on the third floor,
我在三楼
so I don't have to move anywhere.
所以我不必搬到任何地方。
- My battery's almost dead. I'm on the move.
-我的电池快没电了。我在移动。
I am out in the open. I am exposed right now.
我在露天。我现在暴露了。
- We are now ascending from the second floor to the third,
-我们现在从二楼升至三楼，
where Ben and Jake reside.
本和杰克居住的地方。
Let's start off here. We're gonna do a sweep.
让我们从这里开始。我们要去扫一扫。
We're gonna hit every room and work our way around.
我们要打每个房间，努力解决。
(suspenseful music)
（悬疑的音乐）
- Oh, I see him.
-哦，我看见他。
Weddle, no I saw you.
ed，不，我没看见你。
- Go that way. I'm goin' this way.
-往那边走。我要这样
- Weddle no.
-结婚号
- Weddle.
-结婚了。
- I've known all along. I'm so tired.
-我一直都知道。我好累。
I haven't eaten since three p.m.
我从下午三点开始就没吃饭
(laughs)
（笑）
- Jake, your fly is also down
-杰克，你的苍蝇也落下了
not to add insult to injury.
不要增加侮辱性伤害。
- Let's not tell Ben (laughs).
-我们不告诉本（笑）。
- Should we just go home, forget about Ben?
-我们应该回家吗，忘掉Ben？
- Yeah, I think we should probably just head out.
-是的，我想我们应该出去吧。
- What up?
- 怎么了？
(laughs) dude, that's a good spot.
（笑）老兄，那是个好地方。
- Ben, come on out
-本，快出来
(laughs)
（笑）
- How good is that spot?
-那地方好吗？
The winner of the $50,000 game of hide and seek is Ben.
本次50,000美元捉迷藏游戏的赢家是Ben。
(group cheers)
（团体欢呼）
We need to let Weddle into prison.
我们需要让韦德尔入狱。
- To where I belong,
-我属于的地方
this is what prison's like kids.
这就是监狱里的孩子。
(laughs)
（笑）
- All right Ben, now I'm gonna awkwardly hand you
-好吧，本，我要尴尬地交给你
the money in front of everyone.
钱摆在大家面前。
(applause)
（掌声）
Maybe you should buy them some stuff, I dunno.
不知道，也许您应该给他们买些东西。
Subscribe. I hope you enjoyed. Goodbye.
订阅。希望您喜欢。再见。
- It was such a good time
-那真是太好了
and now I'm gonna be able to actually give my family
现在我将能够真正给我的家人
and everything a good Christmas, you know?
一切都很好，圣诞节，你知道吗？
I'm really excited.
我很激动。
- Well, Ben, congratulations.
-好的，本，恭喜。
Enjoy your 50 grand.
享受您的50盛大。
- Thanks, man.
- 谢啦。
(explosion) ♪ Mister Beast, ohhh ♪
（爆炸）♪野兽先生，哦♪